Unexpected girl.
I got it.
It's funny.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Good morning.
Today, we are going to play a game
called,
Kareta Queen, by Kareta.
Wow, that's right.
I think Kareta is a winter game.
It's winter now.
Oh, it's winter now.
Yes, it's winter now.
You are so bold.
I'm the first one to play.
I started playing Kareta from making my
own character.
That's fun.
You make your own character from paper?
Yes, I make my own character from
paper.
I'm so excited.
The content of Kareta is,
you make a character and a reading card
with the character you have in your
hand.
Then, you play Kareta.
That's fun.
There are 8 people today.
You will play Kareta with 4 people.
The winner will play Kareta with 4
people.
I see.
So, let's make a Kareta together.
Let's do it.
Let's make Kareta.
Okay.
That's funny.
So, let's make a Kareta.
You may not know many things about
Tohoku,
so I hope you enjoy reading Kareta.
Let's do it.
Red, yellow, blue, green, black,
yellow, red.
I thought of yellow.
It's fun.
Is it?
I only wrote Hiragana.
Let's do Kareta.
Kareta?
Yua is cute.
Please subscribe to this channel.
I'm not the first one.
I see.
You are cute.
I asked her if she was not the first
one.
She said she was not the first one.
I see.
If I find the first one,
I can find many cute girls,
but I can't find the second one.
I'm not the first one.
I see.
You are cute.
I have a lot of free time.
Free time!
That's funny.
Write it down.
That's crazy.
I have a lot of free time.
I'm sorry.
I'll tell you the truth.
That's crazy.
I have a lot of free time.
I don't have free time.
That's crazy.
There are things that can't be done
even if you tell me.
Because you're human.
I'm a human.
It's funny.
It's good.
We're done.
It's long.
We did it.
First, we'll divide it into four
people.
Let's divide it in the middle.
Let's start with the left team.
Yes.
Yay!
The first round, Iginari Touhoku-san's
usual karta.
Start!
I'll start.
She talks too much and is long.
That's fast.
I'll start.
She dances like a Souranbushi.
That's fast.
That's it!
Souranbushi!
I've never danced.
I'll start.
She's slow to decide the content of the
live.
That's amazing.
She's a bad talker.
It's about us, so it's fine.
It's fun.
She's a bad talker.
Don't say it.
That's funny.
She's a bad talker.
I'll start.
She can't enter the store with 9
people.
That's wrong.
She's a bad talker.
It's a good opportunity!
I'm not good at this.
Don't worry. I'm not going to touch
you.
I was surprised that you were 3 years
older than me.
You're so passionate.
I'm going to do it.
I was a mother of a child.
I see.
Who wrote this?
What does this mean?
It's a personality of motherhood.
I can't do it even if I'm born.
Hinao
I got it.
I'm selling KUINI-ANMA.
Ramen is delicious.
What is that?
Rabbit angel and Mako girl.
That's great.
There are two more.
Thank you for watching.
I can't drink it without compliments.
See you next time!
Great!
That was a good line.
It was a good match.
What is your score, Hatsuki?
8 points.
4 points.
17 points.
It was the same.
5 points.
Since we are here, let's make it a tie.
Great!
It was a good match.
Thank you for watching!
Hello, This is Round 2!
Good Luck!
eto the start!
To the first turn,
Go behind with mind's eye!
Bye bye!
This looks like a water scene.
It's difficult.
I can't think of anything.
It's okay.
I'll start.
The clothes that are scattered and
dropped in the water are all messed up.
I got it.
The word that makes you feel like
you're going to be in trouble.
Cute.
Dan-chan is a greeting and a song.
I've never seen that.
I'm going to take a video.
Makeup time is 2 hours.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I'm scared.
She talks a lot of nonsense.
She is strong.
It was painful.
I'll go.
Tacos are popular at one time.
It's difficult.
It's not popular.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Q. Who is the most likely to be a good
friend of you?
A. Hima, the light girl.
That's a lie.
Q. Who is the most likely to be a good
friend of you?
A. Jaws, the grandchild.
Jaws?
No, it's not.
It's a lie.
Q. Who is the most likely to be a good
friend of you?
A. Isaka, the cringe queen.
It's a lie.
Karin's curling Center
You're in the frame!
You're touching her so beautifully!
This is fantastic!
I can't die!
I'm glad you're happy.
I'm so happy.
I'll go.
I often say to adults,
you're tall.
I think so.
Don't do the live.
I'm going to do it.
It was amazing.
It looks fun.
I'll praise you for everything.
I thought it was a no.
Hirano is cute, too.
This?
Hirano.
The end.
Thank you for watching.
I'm so disappointed.
I wanted to eat the Almond.
I wanted to eat it.
Can I read it?
Let's do it.
I want to read it.
Let's count it.
I'm glad I got it.
I'll do my best.
I'll never eat it again.
Yeah!
The final match of Iginari Tohoku's 〇〇
Karuta.
Ryo! Ka! Ru! Ta!
Wow!
It's not that great.
What's Karuta?
Please be excited.
You're calm.
Look at this.
I'm not good at this.
Do your best.
I can see your smile.
You're addicted.
I'll do my best.
I'm not good at this.
Ritsuki is next.
Who is she?
I'm going to do my best.
I'll go to a restaurant when I'm
stressed.
I'll go to a club.
That's a prefectural competition.
You're too much.
I'm not good at this.
I'm not good at wearing a topknot.
I'm not good at wearing a necklace.
I'll do my best.
Miyagi is going to win.
I don't want to walk on the flat
ground.
Please look forward to the next video!
That's all for today!
I'm so nervous.
How do you feel now?
I'm going to die.
I don't want to die.
Good luck.
I love you, Kurie.
I love you, too.
Thank you.
The first question.
I love delicious food.
It's a prefecture-level competition.
Everyone is a representative of the
prefecture-level competition.
Yomitama is a representative of the
I'm nervous.
I like salmon.
Good luck.
Here, here.
What does this mean?
I'm in trouble.
I love salmon.
I'll go.
I'm going to open my bag.
I'm in trouble.
I have a lot to say.
Go.
The last one.
What is this?
It's a bell of love.
I'm in trouble.
Are you all right?
It's a scream.
It's over.
What was that?
Good job.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
It was a prefecture-level competition.
A prefecture-level competition.
It was a hand-to-hand competition.
Who is the winner?
Let's count.
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13,14,15.
17,18,19,20,21,22.
Thank you for watching.
Congratulations!
I'm watching you!
I'm so happy!
The first...
The first, the self-made, Iginari,
Tohoku-san, Aruaru-Karuta.
Thank you!
The Queen is...
Akita Prefecture's representative...
I'm not really a representative.
It's Hikari Itsuki!
Congratulations!
If we get more requests for the second
episode,
we'll make it and hold it.
If you have any ideas for the second
episode,
please write them down on your phone.
Even if we don't know what to do,
we can tell everyone what to do.
We can tell them,
we're MCs of the live show.
We want to hear it!
Please write them down!
Thank you!
Please look forward to the next video!
Bye bye!